# ANA TRIPUNOSKA ZDRAVKOVIKJ

### FRONTEND ENGINEER

## CONTACT

+389 70 777 044

atripunoska@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ana-tripunoska

Skopje, North Macedonia

# SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3 / SASS
- JavaScript
- React
- Typescript
- Git
- WordPress
- AFM

# • Team Work

- Adaptability
- Communication
- Problem Solving
- Work Ethic
- Listening

# EDUCATION

2018-2021

**Master of Computer Science and Engineering** 

2011-2017

**Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering** 

SS. Cyril and Methodious University

## LANGUAGES

English - Bilingual

Spanish - Conversational - Level A2

# PUBLICATIONS

Analysis and guidelines for improving the current state of accessibility of Macedonian websites for people with disabilities

\_\_\_\_\_

18th International Conference on Informatics and Information Technologies

### PROFILE

Passionate and meticulous front-end developer with over 7 years of front end experience, striving for continuous self-improvement and making the internet a better (looking) place. Primary focus on converting data to graphical interface for users to view and interact with that data, through digital interaction using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Frontend Engineer**

Valtech | Skopje, North Macedonia

2022 - Present

- Implementing user interface components for web site solutions built with Adobe **Experience Manager**
- Interpreting designs and translating them into pixel-perfect HTML/SCSS/JSX output to create engaging, modern web experiences.
- Ensuring high-performance and compatibility across mobile and desktop browsers using responsive design
- · Developing and testing user-facing features that leverage Vanilla JS, React, **TypeScript**
- Performing bug fixes and code reviews
- Working with experience designers and developers through the stages of design, development, testing, release and maintenance.

# **Frontend Developer**

IWM Network | Skopje, North Macedonia

2016 - 2022

- · Creating, maintaining and improving websites
- · Collaborating with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability
- Building customized features for clients
- Converting PSD files to HTML
- Developing custom WordPress Themes
- **Developing custom Liferay Themes**
- Developing e-commerce websites using WooCommerce
- Implementing On-Page SEO
- Optimizing sites to improve performance and efficiency

# Intern

iBorn | Skopje, North Macedonia

August 2015 - September 2015

- Maintaining Web Applications
- Designing mobile based features
- · Writing functional required documents and guides

